

YEHYA MOUSA

GRAPHIC & WEB DESIGNER

CONTACT

Shibin El-Qanater,Qalyubeia, Egypt

+60 16 41 86 36 5

+20 100 70 64 46 8

yahya.mousa4242@gmail.com

yahya4242.github.io

PERSONAL INFO

NATIONALITY: Egyptian

ETHNICITY: Arab

BIRTH DATE: Nov 18th, 1994

RELIGION: Muslim

MARITAL STATUS: Married

SKILLS

- Microsoft Office.
- Adobe Photoshop.
- Adobe Illustrator.
- Adobe Indesign.
- Corel Draw.
- HTML & HTML5.
- CSS & CSS3 & Bootstrap.
- Javascript.

LANGUAGE

ARABIC & ENGLISH



ABOUT ME

First off, I can see that my skills match the job's description and that's why I'm applying to this position, since I'm planning to relocate to Malaysia to reunite with my family.

I'm an enthusiast, fast learner and ambitious person, and always developing my skills, I've worked in various fields occupying different roles, which gave me good experience that ranges from customer service to management roles.



EDUCATION

Ain - Shams University

Aug 2013 - Oct 2018

B.Sc. in Commerce, Major: Accounting, CGPA: 75%

Udacity

Feb 2020 - May 2020

1 Million Arab Coders, Front-end Development track

Udacity

Aug 2020 - Nov 2020

Web Development Professional Nanodegree



EXPERIENCE

Web Developer - Freelancer

May 2020 - Present

I'm an enthusiast web developer who always aspire to sharpen my knowledge and gain more knowledge everyday, I use HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and Javascript to build front-end websites and Landing pages.

Graphic Designer - Digital Product House (DPH)

Mar 2019 - Present

Working as a senior graphic designer where my roles activities are -but not limited to:

- * Create different designs and illustrations.
- * Prepare different works for digital or offeset printing.
- * Design and supervise the design team to create new concepts that match the client's expectations.
- * Prepare and supervise the production process including CNC operations like: Laser, Router & Plasma works.

Graphic Designer - ADVO Print

Sep 2015 - Oct 2018

Working as a graphic designer with main responsibilities like:

- * Dealing with clients and liaise with them along the production process from scratch to finish.
- * Making and preparing designs for production.
- * Supervising the production process and ensuring it is going according to the plan.